bedbugger.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy for Bedbugger.com — Bedbugger.com

**Privacy Policy for Bedbugger.com**

Definitions: “we” and “us” below refer to Bedbugger.com. “You” and “visitors” below refer to anyone who reads, comments, or posts in the forums.

The privacy of our visitors to Bedbugger.com is important to us.

At Bedbugger.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Bedbugger.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Email Addresses, phone numbers, names

The email address you use to register or post can be seen by us, but we do not share this with third parties.  We can’t be responsible for deleting email addresses or phone numbers you choose to post. We ask that you consider carefully whether you wish to use your real name on Bedbugger.com or not, before posting.

We may email you at the address provided in your profile in connection with your site use.

Log Files

When you visit the Site, we may collect certain non-personally-identifiable information from you, including your IP address, browser type and language, the domain name from which you accessed the Site and the date and time of your visit. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other clickstream data.

The “Clustermap” on the blog sidebar, which shows the location of recent visitors, is one example of how the IP information is used (in aggregate form and anonymously).

Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to collect the non-personal information described above. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the Site. We may also use cookies to: (1) allow you to use the Site without having to re-enter your user name and password; (2) monitor Site usage; (3) manage the Site; and (4) improve the Site and our services. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

We may also use web beacons on the Site, in our emails and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your Site visit, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and/or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. Web beacons help us analyze our Site visitors’ behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Site and our advertising. We may work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyze this information. In addition, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site and to serve our advertisements across the Internet. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Third-party advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Chicago-related ads to someone in Chicago, for example).

We show ads from third-party vendors which may include those listed on the following page [What vendors are certified for third-party ads? (Google)](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149). You may visit those vendor websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor offers this capability).

Ads you see on this and other websites may be based in part on your previous actions on visits over time and on various websites. This is known as “interest-based” or “online behavioral” advertising, and you may [visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s website to opt out of interest-based advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/?partnerId=1//#completed "Opt out of interest based advertising").

Google DART Cookie

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information ( **not** including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here to read [Advertising and Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) from Google.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) This will change the Google ads you see on Bedbugger.com and on other sites where Google ads are shown.

Other uses of information

We may use your information (including IP address, ISP, email, and other information provided by you or otherwise tracked as noted above) to enforce Bedbugger.com’s [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://bedbugger.com/terms-conditions "Terms and Conditions of Site User") or prevent or respond to improper activity related to the site or to prevent or respond to illegal activity.  In the event of suspected illegal activity, this information may be shared with law enforcement.

Contact Form

We use a secure [contact form](http://bedbugger.com/about/contact "Contact form"). If you choose to send a message via the contact form, it will go to nobugsonme, the site owner.

_  
*This statement was based in part on a template by[JenSense.](http://www.jensense.com/2008/03/05/adsense-friendly-privacy-policy-sample-for-adsense-publishers-to-use/ "jensense") Thanks JenSense!_

CHANGES:

Updated 9/17/2012:

  * Section on “Email Addresses, phone numbers, names”: added:

> “We may email you at the address provided in your profile in connection with your site use.”

  * Added link to contact form

Added 9/17/2012:

  * Added new section: Other uses of information

> “We may use your information (including IP address, ISP, email, and other information provided by you or otherwise tracked as noted above) to enforce Bedbugger.com’s [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://bedbugger.com/terms-conditions "Terms and Conditions of Site User") or prevent or respond to improper activity related to the site or to prevent or respond to illegal activity.  In the event of suspected illegal activity, this information may be shared with law enforcement.”

Edited  4/16/2014:

  * Adding additional information to “Cookies and Web Beacons”, minor edits to “Log Files” section, and
  * Adding an opt-out link for interest-based advertising.
